One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
.مشغل الفيديو الخاص بك لا يدعم صيغة ملف الترجمة المستخدمة في هذه الحلقة .من المحتمل ألا تعمل الترجمة بشكل صحيح يرجى استخدام أحد مشغلات الفيديو :على سبيل المثال mpv الموصى بها، كمشغل https://mpv.io/
H-He just...
...هـ-هذا الوغد
He broke Captain Kuro's cat claw!
!كسر مخالب القط التي تخصّ القبطان كورو
Only five of these weird sword things left!
!تبقت خمسة من هذه السيوف الغريبة
It's okay! He has plenty of fight left in him!
!لا بأس! لا يزال يستطيع القتال
Yeah! He's still got the other claw!
!صحيح! لا يزال لديه المخلب الآخر
Scratch him up and kill him, Captain Kuro!
!اخدشه واقتله أيّها القبطان كورو
Whoa, you can't call him that anymore!
!مهلًا، هذا الاسم محظور
Oh yeah... I think his name in the village was Klaha... something...
.أعتقد أنّ اسمه في هذه القرية كلاها-شيء
– Mr. Klah! Get 'im!
!نل منه يا كلا-سان
Would you all just...
...أيمكنكم
shut the hell up?!
!التزام الصمت؟...
Come on out, you twerps!
!اخرجوا أيّها الأطفال
I know you're hiding in there!
!أعلم أنّكم مختبئون هناك
Give it up already!
!استسلموا
Come over here!
،تعال إلى هنا
We'll take you straight to her!
.سندلّك على مكان كايا-سان
You really think I'm that gullible? As if I'd trust anything you brats say!
!وكأنّ هذه الحيلة ستنطلي عليّ، لا أثق بما يقوله أطفال
Huh?!
!ماذا؟
We got him!
!وقع في الفخ
Now!
!الآن
Take this!
!خذ هذه
Pepper Attack!
كونشو كوغيكي
– Push!
...ادفعا
Owww!
!مؤلم
Ow! Ow!
!مؤلم! مؤلم
– It's over, hypnotist!
!هذه النهاية أيّها المنوّم المغناطيسي
Don't get cocky.
!لا تغتروا بأنفسكم
Darn it! We failed...!
!تبًّا، أخفقنا
You've made a mockery of me.
...إنكم تستخفون بي
But I am still a pirate...
...لكنّني قرصان
– Onion!
!تامانيغي
You wannabe pirate brats poked your noses in a bit too deep...
...تماديتم كثيرًا بلعبة القراصنة هذه
Where are you hiding, Miss?!
أين تختبئين أيّتها الآنسة؟
I'll start by executing these three.
.سأبدأ بإعدام هؤلاء الثلاثة
You can reflect on your poor choice to meddle with real pirates...
فكّروا مليًا بحماقة التدخل في قتال قراصنة حقيقي جيّدًا
on your way to the afterlife.
في العالم الآخر
There you are.
.أنتِ هناك إذًا
No!
!لا
Run, Miss Kaya!
!اهربي يا كايا-سان
Hey!
!اسمع
Yeah! That's them!
!أجل، إنّه صوتهم
It's the other way?!
!الجانب الآخر؟
I'll eliminate each and every one of you later...
...سأقضي عليكم جميعًا لاحقًا
That includes Jango!
!وطبعًا... جانغو الوغد أيضًا
Please stop joking around, Captain Kuro!
!دع عنك المزاح أيها القبطان كورو
It's still not too late for us to attack the village, right?!
لم يفت أوان هجومنا على القرية
And if Captain Jango gets her to write her will, your plan will succeed!
وأيضًا، إن تمكّن القبطان جانغو من جعل تلك الفتاة تكتب وصيتها
Do not concern yourselves with the details of my plan...
،لا داعي لقلقكم على الخطة
All I need from you are corpses on which to pin the blame.
...جثثكم وحدها كافية لإلقاء اللوم عليكم
I never intended to let any of you leave this village alive.
...لم أنوِ السماح لكم بمغادرة هذه القرية من الأساس
I can't let anyone who knows my true identity live.
لا يمكنني السّماح بعيشِ من يعلم بأنني لا أزال حيًّا
No way...
!لا يعقل
Then you planned to kill us from the very start?!
!كانت خطتك هي أن تقتلنا منذ البداية إذًا؟
That's right...
...صحيح
For three long years now, back when I was still going by Captain Kuro...
...منذ ثلاث سنين حين كنت لا أزال أُعرف باسم القبطان كورو
it was all...
...كان كلّ ذلك
it was all part of my plan!
!جزءًا من خطتي...
Man, you guys are dumb.
أأنتم حمقى؟
Your pirate crew is so lame!
!يا لفظاعتكم من مجموعة قراصنة
"Lame"?
فظاعتنا؟
In the end, a pirate crew is nothing but a pack of stray dogs!
!مجموعات القراصنة ليست إلّا تجمّعًا للمنبوذين اجتماعيًا
What could they possibly accomplish without a plan?!
ماذا يمكنهم فعله دون الخطط؟
Every last one should just shut up and follow my orders!
!على كلّ منهم أن يصمت ويتّبع خطّتي فحسب
Crew members are a captain's loyal pawns!
!أفراد الطاقم هم بيادق مخلصة للقبطان
I'm the one who decides whether to kill them or spare them.
!بقاء رجالي أحياء أو لا كلّه يقع تحت إمرتي بصفتي قبطانهم
No matter how great the obstacle, they simply need to stand up to it...
...مهما كان العائق كبيرًا، عليهم فقط مواجهته
and die according to my plans.
.والتضحية بحياتهم من أجل خطتي
This is what it means to be a pirate!
!هذا هو أسلوب القراصنة
Don't patronize me, you little vagrant!
!لا تتحدّث بتعالٍ معي أيّها الطفل الرحال
Even if a captain like you...
،إن كنت أنت القبطان
had hundreds or thousands of men following him...
،فحتّى لو اتبعك مئات أو آلاف الرجال
you'd never be better than Usopp!
!فلن تنتصر على أوسوب أبدًا
What?!
!ماذا؟
You're saying I'm inferior to a kid pretending to be a pirate captain?
أتقول إني أقل شأنًا من طفل يلعب دور قبطان قراصنة؟
That's right!
.صحيح
How droll!
!هذا مضحك
Don't get cocky just because you snapped one of my claws!
لا تغتر بنفسك لمجرد كسرك لأحد مخلبيَّ
How exactly is he better than me?!
ما الذي لا أستطيع الانتصار عليه به؟
Let's hear it!
!أخبرني
Character.
.الشخصية
What?!
!ماذا؟
You have no idea what it means to be a pirate!
!أنت لا تعرف شيم القرصان الحقيقي
H-He...
...لـ-لقد
He kept up with the Pussyfoot Maneuver!
!واكب سرعة قدم التسلّل...
How insulting...
...يا للإهانة
If you're curious about real pirates, then allow me to demonstrate...
...إن كنت تريد معرفة شيم القراصنة الحقيقيين إلى هذا الحد، فسأريك
true terror.
...رهبتهم
The terror of a pirate who has faced death countless times!
!رهبة قرصان واجه الموت مرّات عديدة
Hey! That stance! Is he...?!
...تلك الوقفة! لا يمكن
That's the move he's gonna use?!
!سيستخدم تلك التقنية؟
But he's only fighting one guy!
!ولكنّه يقاتل شخصًا واحدًا فقط
But that's definitely it!
!لكن لا شك بذلك
He's planning to use Whole Nine Yarns!
!شاكشي، سيستخدم شاكشي
Aren't we in danger here?!
أليس من الخطر أن نكون هنا؟
He'll get us, too!
!سيقضي علينا أيضًا
He already plans to kill us!
!إنّه ينوي قتلنا أيضًا
He even said so earlier!
!قال ذلك قبل قليل
Please stop, Captain Kuro!
!أرجوك توقف أيّها القبطان كورو
Anything but that!
!أيّ شيء سوى هذه التقنية
We'll do anything you want!
!سنفعل أيّ ما تريده
Please, Captain Kuro!
!نتوسّل إليكَ أيّها القبطان كورو
What's the big deal?
ما خطبهم؟
He's just swaying back and forth...
...إنّه يترنّح فحسب
– Please stop, Captain Kuro!
!لا تفعلها
Whole Nine Yarns!
شاكشي
What a pitiful haul...
!ما أقلّها من غنيمة
I thought they'd have a little more treasure than that...
...اعتقدت أنَّ بحوزتهم كنزًا أكبر من هذا
Let's see, is the fight over yet?
فلنرَ... هل انتهى القتال؟
What?
ماذا؟
Nobody's moving...
...الجميع متوقفون
Is it over?
هل انتهى؟
There it is!
!ها هو
Wh-Why's he over there?!
!لـ-لماذا هناك؟
Not again!
!ثانيةً
Now it's the wall!
!الحائط هذه المرة
Please stop, Captain Kuro!
!أرجوك توقف أيّها القبطان كورو
It's no use! His Pussyfoot Maneuver attacks are out of control!
!لا فائدة! إنّه يهاجم بعشوائيّة عندما يستخدم قدم التسلّل
He's moving so fast he doesn't even know what he's slashing!
!بسبب سرعته، فحتّى هو نفسه لا يعرف ما الذي يقطعه
He's already cut down so many of our cr–
...وقع عديد من رفاقنا ضحايا لهذه الـ
Wh-What's happening?!
مـ-ماذا يجري؟
They're getting all sliced up out of nowhere!
!إنّهم يُقطعون فجأة
Show yourself...
...اظهر أيّها
butler...
الخادم
Don't you care about your crew at all?!
من هم رفاقك في رأيك؟
Luffy...
...لوفي
Found you!
!وجدتك
Sly bastard!
!أيّها اللعين
You should've let me cut you down like a good little boy!
.كان عليك أن تُقطع بهدوء فحسب
Look!
!انظر
My poor men are suffering dearly, and it's all thanks to you!
رجالي الظريفون بقوا أحياء ومتألمين بفضلك
It would've been kinder if you'd just let my attack kill them!
.كان من الأفضل أن يموتوا بذلك
Now what?
ماذا الآن؟
You look like you have something to say...
.يبدو أنّ هناك ما تريد قوله
Yeah...
...أجل
No matter what...
...لن أصبح
I will never be like you.
.رجلًا مثلك أبدًا
Never will...?
.«ليس «لن تصبح
More like never can. Not someone like you, anyway.
!بل أنّ فتًى مثلك لا يستطيع أن يكون مثلي
Though it doesn't matter...
...لاسيّما
since you're going to die here anyway.
أنّك ستموت هنا
Please stop this!
!أرجوك توقف
Leave them alone!
!لا تمسّهم بسوء
I'll write the will!
!سأكتب وصيّتي
N-No!
!لـ-لا
They'll kill you if you write it, Miss Kaya!
!ستقتلين إن كتبتها يا كايا-سان
You've got the wrong idea. There are no negotiations to be had here.
،أيتها الحمقاء
Captain Kuro told me to get rid of everyone.
.أخبرني القبطان كورو أن أتخلّص من الجميع
You can't be serious!
!لا يمكن
Do as I say, or I'll take my own life!
!إن لم تفعل ما أقوله، فلن تتمكن من قتلي
That means no will!
!ولن أكتب وصيتي أيضًا
Wh-Wh-Whoa! Just hold on!
!تـ-تمهلي
Don't be hasty!
!لا تتهوري
I absolutely must get you to write that will!
!عليك أن تكتبي الوصية مهما حدث
M-Miss Kaya!
!كـ-كايا-سان
Fine! The twerps can go!
!حسنًا، سأخلي سبيل الأطفال
Though they're really in no condition to run...
وإن كانوا في حالةٍ لا تسمح لهم بالهرب
Sign it, too!
!لا تنسي أن توقّعي
I know...
.أعلم
"I leave my entire estate to my butler, Klahadore..."
«أترك كلّ ثروتي إلى خادمي كلاهادور»
Excellent!
!ممتاز
This is your will, all right!
،هذه وصيتك حقًّا
And I didn't even have to hypnotize you!
.وفّر عليّ هذا عناء تنويمك مغناطيسيًا
You promise not to kill them, right?
ألم تعدني أنّك لن تقتلهم؟
Don't worry.
.لا تقلقي
I might not look like it, but I'm a man of my word.
.رغم مظهري، إلّا أنّي معروف بكوني رجل صادق
– Miss Kaya!
!كايا-سان
There they are!
!وجدتهم
There they are! There they are! Stop!
!وجدتهم! وجدتهم! وجدتهم! توقف
Owww! Ow, ow, ow!
!مؤلم! مؤلم! مؤلم
That's where I got cut, you know!
!لديّ جرح هنا
Over there!
!هناك
Alright, I'll be back!
!حسنٌ، سأذهب
That's far enough, hypno-freak!
!هذا يكفي أيّها المنوّم المغناطيسي اللعين
He came after me?!
!لحقني إلى هنا؟
Guess I'd better finish this quickly!
!الظاهر أن الأفضل أن أنهي هذا سريعًا
Everything before now was just an appetizer.
.كان كلّ شيء حتّى الآن مجرد لهو
You get the three-course treatment.
.سأمنحك معاملة خاصة
I will baste you in terror and serve you meticulously on a platter!
!سأذيقك طعم الرعب، ومن ثم أطبخك ببطء
Whole Nine Yarns!
شاكشي
Just try that foot technique now!
!جرّب تقنية القدم تِلك الآن
Curses! Get off of me!
!تبًا! ابتعد عنّي أيّها اللعين
Now your three-year plan is a complete failure!
!وبهذا، فشلت خطتك ذات السنين الثلاثة تمامًا
What?!
!ماذا؟
He caught Captain Kuro!
!أمسك بالقبطان كورو
Hey, if he wins, that means we won't get killed, right?!
!هل يعقل أنّه إن انتصر، فلن نُقتل؟
Now you die!
!فلتموتي
Oh, no, you don't!
!لن نسمح لك
You damn kids!
!أيّها الأطفال الأوغاد
You're just one step too late, bellyband!
!يبدو أنّك تأخرت في خطوة واحدة يا صاحب الهاماراكي
You sure about that?
!لا أوافقك
Yes! That branch was in the way!
!صحيح، كان ذلك الغصن يعيقني
What?!
ماذا؟
Usopp...
...أوسوب-سان
– Captain!
!القبطان
Eat this, hypnotist!
!خذ هذه أيّها المنوّم المغناطيسي
Get 'im, rubber guy!
!نل منه أيّها المطاطي
Kick Captain Kuro's ass!
!أبرح القبطان كورو ضربًا
Get away!
!ابتعد
You guys don't get to cheer for me!
!لا يحق لكم تشجيعي
Let go!
!اتركني
Gum-Gum...
غومو غومو نو
Lethal Exploding Star!
هيساتسو كاياكو بوشي
...Bell!
الجرس